<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teaching | Your Name</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/teaching/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/teaching/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Teaching</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_bf586d412669769d.png</url>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/teaching/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 202 - Mind and Society</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory psychology course examining psychological and social processes across the lifespan. Topics include human development, motivation and emotion, health and well-being, social influence, personality, psychological disorders, and treatment approaches. Part of the introductory psychology sequence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-gtf&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GTF&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored weekly lab sections led by undergraduate peer leaders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held office hours for student support and questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitated discussion forum participation on Canvas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supported students with weekly assignments and assessments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped coordinate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-structure&#34;&gt;Course Structure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course combined multiple learning modalities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Interactive online demonstrations of psychological concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive quizzing to reinforce learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discussion forums&lt;/strong&gt;: Online discussions of course topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lab sections&lt;/strong&gt;: Peer-led small group sessions (which I supervised)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Hands-on exposure to psychological research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Assessments of course content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-experience&#34;&gt;Teaching Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position provided valuable experience in supervising undergraduate teaching assistants and managing online discussion forums. I learned to balance supporting peer leaders while ensuring quality educational experiences for students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 301 - Scientific Thinking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-301/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-301/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A course focused on developing critical thinking skills for evaluating psychological research. Students learn to read empirical articles, assess research validity, and understand the scientific method as applied to psychology. This course prepares students for upper-division psychology courses and research experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held weekly office hours to support students with coursework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted students in understanding and critiquing research articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped clarify concepts related to research design and validity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provided feedback on assignments and supported the grading process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answered student questions about research methods and interpretation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-assessment-components&#34;&gt;Course Assessment Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I supported students across multiple assignment types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (40%): Weekly adaptive quizzes on research concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Article worksheet&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Guided analysis of an empirical research article&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Validity review&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Critical evaluation of research design and validity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-class assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Active learning exercises during class time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experience deepened my ability to teach research methodology to students with varying levels of statistical and scientific background. I became more effective at helping students transition from passive consumers of research to critical evaluators of scientific claims.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 201 - Mind and Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory course exploring the biological and cognitive foundations of psychology. Topics include brain structure and function, sensation and perception, consciousness, learning and memory, and the neural basis of behavior. This course is part of the introductory psychology sequence and fulfills general education requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Served as primary point of contact for assigned group of students (alphabetically divided among GEs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held regular office hours to answer student questions and provide academic support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored and supported student engagement with course technology (iClicker, InQuizitive, ZAPS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped students navigate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-components&#34;&gt;Course Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course included multiple interactive elements that I supported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iClicker participation&lt;/strong&gt;: In-class polling and engagement activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive online quizzes to reinforce concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Online interactive demonstrations of psychological phenomena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Students completed psychology studies or alternative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Four exams covering course material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role strengthened my ability to explain complex neuroscience concepts to introductory students and manage multiple student support responsibilities simultaneously. Working with online learning platforms also enhanced my digital teaching skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 302 - Statistical Methods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-302/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A foundational course in statistical methods for psychology, building on Scientific Thinking (PSY 301) and preparing students for Research Methods (PSY 303). Topics include descriptive statistics, probability, hypothesis testing, correlation, ANOVA, and regression. Students gain hands-on experience with statistical software (Jamovi) and learn to interpret and report analyses using APA style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held regular office hours to help students with statistical concepts and assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led weekly lab sections to teach Jamovi software and statistical analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provided support for weekly homework assignments and quizzes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped students troubleshoot data analysis problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and exam preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-components&#34;&gt;Course Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I supported students across multiple learning activities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lab sections&lt;/strong&gt; (5%): Hands-on practice with Jamovi statistical software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamovi homework assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Weekly data analysis problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly quizzes&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Online assessments of statistical concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-class activities&lt;/strong&gt; (5%): Interactive exercises during lectures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt; (50%): Two midterms and a cumulative final&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-approach&#34;&gt;Teaching Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In lab sections, I emphasized conceptual understanding alongside computational skills. I worked to demystify statistics by connecting abstract concepts to concrete research examples and helping students develop intuition for when to apply different statistical tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teaching statistics strengthened my own quantitative skills and taught me how to explain complex mathematical concepts in accessible ways. I became more proficient with statistical software and learned effective strategies for helping students overcome statistics anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
