<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Your Name</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Your Name</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_bf586d412669769d.png</url>
      <title>Your Name</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 202 - Mind and Society</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory psychology course examining psychological and social processes across the lifespan. Topics include human development, motivation and emotion, health and well-being, social influence, personality, psychological disorders, and treatment approaches. Part of the introductory psychology sequence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-gtf&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GTF&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored weekly lab sections led by undergraduate peer leaders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held office hours for student support and questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitated discussion forum participation on Canvas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supported students with weekly assignments and assessments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped coordinate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-structure&#34;&gt;Course Structure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course combined multiple learning modalities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Interactive online demonstrations of psychological concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive quizzing to reinforce learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discussion forums&lt;/strong&gt;: Online discussions of course topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lab sections&lt;/strong&gt;: Peer-led small group sessions (which I supervised)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Hands-on exposure to psychological research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Assessments of course content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-experience&#34;&gt;Teaching Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position provided valuable experience in supervising undergraduate teaching assistants and managing online discussion forums. I learned to balance supporting peer leaders while ensuring quality educational experiences for students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 301 - Scientific Thinking</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-301/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-301/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A course focused on developing critical thinking skills for evaluating psychological research. Students learn to read empirical articles, assess research validity, and understand the scientific method as applied to psychology. This course prepares students for upper-division psychology courses and research experiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held weekly office hours to support students with coursework&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted students in understanding and critiquing research articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped clarify concepts related to research design and validity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provided feedback on assignments and supported the grading process&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answered student questions about research methods and interpretation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-assessment-components&#34;&gt;Course Assessment Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I supported students across multiple assignment types:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (40%): Weekly adaptive quizzes on research concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Article worksheet&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Guided analysis of an empirical research article&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Validity review&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Critical evaluation of research design and validity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-class assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Active learning exercises during class time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This experience deepened my ability to teach research methodology to students with varying levels of statistical and scientific background. I became more effective at helping students transition from passive consumers of research to critical evaluators of scientific claims.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personality Traits and Health Behavior Change: A Longitudinal Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/example-paper-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/example-paper-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is your featured publication. You can add more details here about the study, including additional context about methodology, implications, or links to supplementary materials.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Academic Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome&#34;&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my website. I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in Psychology at University Name, where I work with Prof. Advisor Name studying social and health psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-research-interests&#34;&gt;My Research Interests&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research examines how psychological and social factors influence health and well-being. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly interested in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personality and health&lt;/strong&gt;: How individual differences shape health behaviors and outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social relationships&lt;/strong&gt;: The role of social support in buffering stress and promoting resilience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health behavior change&lt;/strong&gt;: Developing effective interventions tailored to individual characteristics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Longitudinal methods&lt;/strong&gt;: Understanding how these processes unfold over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-find-here&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Find Here&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this site, you&amp;rsquo;ll find:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My published research papers and conference presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing research projects and collaborations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blog posts about graduate school, research methods, and psychology topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information about my teaching and mentoring experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resources for students interested in psychology research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-i-do-this-work&#34;&gt;Why I Do This Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about understanding the psychological mechanisms that promote health and well-being because this knowledge can inform interventions that actually help people. My goal is to conduct rigorous, open science that makes a real difference in people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in Touch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m always interested in connecting with other researchers, potential collaborators, or students interested in psychology. Feel free to reach out via email or connect with me on social media!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/experience/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 201 - Mind and Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory course exploring the biological and cognitive foundations of psychology. Topics include brain structure and function, sensation and perception, consciousness, learning and memory, and the neural basis of behavior. This course is part of the introductory psychology sequence and fulfills general education requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Served as primary point of contact for assigned group of students (alphabetically divided among GEs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held regular office hours to answer student questions and provide academic support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored and supported student engagement with course technology (iClicker, InQuizitive, ZAPS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped students navigate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-components&#34;&gt;Course Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course included multiple interactive elements that I supported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iClicker participation&lt;/strong&gt;: In-class polling and engagement activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive online quizzes to reinforce concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Online interactive demonstrations of psychological phenomena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Students completed psychology studies or alternative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Four exams covering course material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role strengthened my ability to explain complex neuroscience concepts to introductory students and manage multiple student support responsibilities simultaneously. Working with online learning platforms also enhanced my digital teaching skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stress and Coping Longitudinal Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/ml-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/ml-framework/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ongoing longitudinal project tracks 300 college students across their undergraduate years to understand how stress and coping strategies evolve over time and influence mental health outcomes. We collect data through:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Semester surveys&lt;/strong&gt;: Comprehensive assessments of stress, coping, personality, and well-being&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily diaries&lt;/strong&gt;: Brief daily reports of stressors and mood (2-week bursts each semester)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Physiological data&lt;/strong&gt;: Optional cortisol samples during exam periods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Academic records&lt;/strong&gt;: GPA and course completion data (with consent)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;key-research-questions&#34;&gt;Key Research Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do coping strategies change as students progress through college?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Which personality traits predict adaptive vs. maladaptive coping?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do certain coping patterns protect against mental health decline during high-stress periods?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How do social support networks moderate stress-health relationships?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;methods-and-tools&#34;&gt;Methods and Tools&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Survey platform: Qualtrics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data analysis: R (lavaan, lme4, ggplot2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily diary: Custom smartphone app&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Open data and code repository on OSF&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;current-status&#34;&gt;Current Status&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are currently in Year 2 of data collection. Preliminary findings have been presented at APS 2023 (see Publications).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;collaboration&#34;&gt;Collaboration&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This project is a collaboration between our lab and the Student Health Center. We are grateful for funding from [Funding Source].&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Tips for Managing Your Research Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/research-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/research-tips/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As I&amp;rsquo;ve progressed through my PhD, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned several strategies that help me stay organized and make steady progress on my research. Here are five tips that have been particularly helpful:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-keep-detailed-records-of-your-work&#34;&gt;1. Keep Detailed Records of Your Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s analysis scripts, IRB protocols, or manuscript drafts—keep everything organized and version-controlled. I use a combination of Google Drive for collaboration and GitHub for analysis scripts. Having a clear folder structure and naming convention has saved me countless times when reviewers ask for additional analyses or when I need to reference earlier versions of a manuscript.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-keep-a-research-journal&#34;&gt;2. Keep a Research Journal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day, I spend 10 minutes writing down what I worked on, what I learned, and what I plan to do next. This helps in several ways:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s easier to write progress reports and papers when you have a detailed record&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can track patterns in your productivity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It forces you to reflect on whether you&amp;rsquo;re making progress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-set-weekly-goals&#34;&gt;3. Set Weekly Goals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the start of each week, I identify 3-5 concrete goals. Not &amp;ldquo;work on paper&amp;rdquo; but &amp;ldquo;write introduction section&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;run experiment X with parameters Y.&amp;rdquo; This makes it easier to know when you&amp;rsquo;ve accomplished something.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-schedule-regular-check-ins&#34;&gt;4. Schedule Regular Check-ins&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meet with your advisor regularly, even when you don&amp;rsquo;t have major updates. Consistent communication helps catch problems early and keeps you accountable. I meet with my advisor every two weeks, and we have a shared document where I update my progress beforehand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-build-a-support-network&#34;&gt;5. Build a Support Network&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grad school can be isolating. Build relationships with other students in your department, join reading groups, and don&amp;rsquo;t be afraid to ask for help. Some of my best ideas have come from casual conversations with peers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion&#34;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These strategies won&amp;rsquo;t work for everyone, and you should adapt them to your own style. The key is to find systems that reduce cognitive load so you can focus your mental energy on the research itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What strategies have worked for you? I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear about them!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personality and Health Behavior Intervention</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/data-visualization/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/data-visualization/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This randomized controlled trial tests whether tailoring health behavior interventions to personality characteristics improves their effectiveness. We recruited 200 sedentary adults and assigned them to either a personality-matched intervention, a generic intervention, or a waitlist control group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;intervention-components&#34;&gt;Intervention Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;personality-matched-condition&#34;&gt;Personality-Matched Condition&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants received personalized feedback and strategies based on their Big Five personality profile:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Conscientiousness&lt;/strong&gt;: Structured goal-setting and scheduling tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Extraversion&lt;/strong&gt;: Group exercise opportunities and social support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Openness&lt;/strong&gt;: Variety in exercise types and novel activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Neuroticism&lt;/strong&gt;: Stress management and self-compassion exercises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Agreeableness&lt;/strong&gt;: Partner accountability and community motivation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;generic-condition&#34;&gt;Generic Condition&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Standard physical activity recommendations and general motivation strategies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;measures&#34;&gt;Measures&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Primary outcome&lt;/strong&gt;: Physical activity (accelerometer data)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Secondary outcomes&lt;/strong&gt;: Self-reported exercise, motivation, self-efficacy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Follow-up&lt;/strong&gt;: 3, 6, and 12 months post-intervention&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;current-status&#34;&gt;Current Status&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We completed data collection in Fall 2023 and are currently analyzing results. Preliminary analyses suggest that personality-matching improves adherence and outcomes, particularly for individuals high in neuroticism.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;implications&#34;&gt;Implications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If successful, this intervention approach could be implemented in clinical and community settings to improve health behavior change outcomes by accounting for individual differences in personality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;funding&#34;&gt;Funding&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supported by a seed grant from the University Research Council.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Support Buffers Stress Effects on Mental Health: Evidence from Daily Diary Study</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/conference-paper-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/conference-paper-2023/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 302 - Statistical Methods</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-302/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-302/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A foundational course in statistical methods for psychology, building on Scientific Thinking (PSY 301) and preparing students for Research Methods (PSY 303). Topics include descriptive statistics, probability, hypothesis testing, correlation, ANOVA, and regression. Students gain hands-on experience with statistical software (Jamovi) and learn to interpret and report analyses using APA style.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held regular office hours to help students with statistical concepts and assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Led weekly lab sections to teach Jamovi software and statistical analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provided support for weekly homework assignments and quizzes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped students troubleshoot data analysis problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and exam preparation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-components&#34;&gt;Course Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I supported students across multiple learning activities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lab sections&lt;/strong&gt; (5%): Hands-on practice with Jamovi statistical software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamovi homework assignments&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Weekly data analysis problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly quizzes&lt;/strong&gt; (20%): Online assessments of statistical concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In-class activities&lt;/strong&gt; (5%): Interactive exercises during lectures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt; (50%): Two midterms and a cumulative final&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-approach&#34;&gt;Teaching Approach&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In lab sections, I emphasized conceptual understanding alongside computational skills. I worked to demystify statistics by connecting abstract concepts to concrete research examples and helping students develop intuition for when to apply different statistical tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Teaching statistics strengthened my own quantitative skills and taught me how to explain complex mathematical concepts in accessible ways. I became more proficient with statistical software and learned effective strategies for helping students overcome statistics anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cultural Differences in Emotional Expression and Well-Being</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publication/workshop-paper-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publication/workshop-paper-2023/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
