<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Introduction | Your Name</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Introduction</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_bf586d412669769d.png</url>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/introduction/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 202 - Mind and Society</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-202/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory psychology course examining psychological and social processes across the lifespan. Topics include human development, motivation and emotion, health and well-being, social influence, personality, psychological disorders, and treatment approaches. Part of the introductory psychology sequence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-gtf&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GTF&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored weekly lab sections led by undergraduate peer leaders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held office hours for student support and questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitated discussion forum participation on Canvas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Supported students with weekly assignments and assessments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped coordinate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-structure&#34;&gt;Course Structure&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course combined multiple learning modalities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Interactive online demonstrations of psychological concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive quizzing to reinforce learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discussion forums&lt;/strong&gt;: Online discussions of course topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lab sections&lt;/strong&gt;: Peer-led small group sessions (which I supervised)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Hands-on exposure to psychological research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Assessments of course content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;teaching-experience&#34;&gt;Teaching Experience&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This position provided valuable experience in supervising undergraduate teaching assistants and managing online discussion forums. I learned to balance supporting peer leaders while ensuring quality educational experiences for students.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Academic Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome&#34;&gt;Welcome!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thank you for visiting my website. I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD student in Psychology at University Name, where I work with Prof. Advisor Name studying social and health psychology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-research-interests&#34;&gt;My Research Interests&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My research examines how psychological and social factors influence health and well-being. I&amp;rsquo;m particularly interested in:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Personality and health&lt;/strong&gt;: How individual differences shape health behaviors and outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Social relationships&lt;/strong&gt;: The role of social support in buffering stress and promoting resilience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health behavior change&lt;/strong&gt;: Developing effective interventions tailored to individual characteristics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Longitudinal methods&lt;/strong&gt;: Understanding how these processes unfold over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-youll-find-here&#34;&gt;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Find Here&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On this site, you&amp;rsquo;ll find:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My published research papers and conference presentations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing research projects and collaborations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blog posts about graduate school, research methods, and psychology topics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Information about my teaching and mentoring experiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resources for students interested in psychology research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;why-i-do-this-work&#34;&gt;Why I Do This Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about understanding the psychological mechanisms that promote health and well-being because this knowledge can inform interventions that actually help people. My goal is to conduct rigorous, open science that makes a real difference in people&amp;rsquo;s lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get in Touch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m always interested in connecting with other researchers, potential collaborators, or students interested in psychology. Feel free to reach out via email or connect with me on social media!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PSY 201 - Mind and Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/teaching/psy-201/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-description&#34;&gt;Course Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An introductory course exploring the biological and cognitive foundations of psychology. Topics include brain structure and function, sensation and perception, consciousness, learning and memory, and the neural basis of behavior. This course is part of the introductory psychology sequence and fulfills general education requirements.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-responsibilities-as-a-ge&#34;&gt;My Responsibilities as a GE&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Served as primary point of contact for assigned group of students (alphabetically divided among GEs)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Held regular office hours to answer student questions and provide academic support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitored and supported student engagement with course technology (iClicker, InQuizitive, ZAPS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisted with grading and course administration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Helped students navigate the research participation requirement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;course-components&#34;&gt;Course Components&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The course included multiple interactive elements that I supported:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;iClicker participation&lt;/strong&gt;: In-class polling and engagement activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;InQuizitive assignments&lt;/strong&gt;: Adaptive online quizzes to reinforce concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ZAPS labs&lt;/strong&gt;: Online interactive demonstrations of psychological phenomena&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research participation&lt;/strong&gt;: Students completed psychology studies or alternative assignments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exams&lt;/strong&gt;: Four exams covering course material&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;skills-developed&#34;&gt;Skills Developed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role strengthened my ability to explain complex neuroscience concepts to introductory students and manage multiple student support responsibilities simultaneously. Working with online learning platforms also enhanced my digital teaching skills.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
